Ernst W. Caspari Papers 1932-1980 Mss.Ms.Coll.1
American Philosophical Society
- Ernst W. Caspari Papers, 1932-1980; 9.5 lin. feet
  - Teicher, Luz S., 1972-1978; 3 folders (57 items) (Box 17)
    Biographical and personal data; Embryology, developmental genetics; Graduate study -- University of Rochester; Mouse genetics; Recommendations
  - Thiele, H. U., 1967 (Box 17)
  - Thompson, William Robert, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Tor, Vedat Nedim, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Touchberry, Robert W., 1968 (Box 17)
  - Tourian, Ara Y., 1974 (Box 17)
  - Truat, W., 1973-1979 (Box 17)
  - Truman, E. R., 1960 (Box 17)
  - Tsujita, Mitsuo, 1963 (Box 17)
  - Turner, Neely, 1960-1962 (Box 17)
  - Tyson, H., 1967 (Box 17)
  - Udry, T. Richard, 1979 (Box 18)
  - United States. Atomic Energy Commission, 1962-1974 (Box 18)
  - Unidentified, 1966-1977 (Box 18)
  - University of Rochester (Box 18)
    - University of Rochester, 1959-1960 (Box 18)
    - Department of Biology (Box 18)
      - Department of Biology, 1969-1979; 4 folders (35 items) (Box 18)
        Committee activities; Educational matters; Evolution; Fellowships, assistantships -- University of Rochester; Graduate study -- University of Rochester; Recommendations; Teaching; University of Rochester
      - Equipment Committee (Box 18)
      - General Info., Pans and Statistics, 1970; 2 folders (Box 18)
      - History (Box 18)
    - Environmental Test Chamber (Box 18)
    - "X" Club, 1962-1966 (Box 18)
  - University of Rochester Medical School, 5 folders (Box 18)
    - University of Rochester Medical School, 1960-1964 (Box 18)
    - Genetics Search Comm., 1975-1978; 4 folders (Box 18)
  - Ursprung, Heinrich, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Vandenberg, Steven G., 1967 (Box 18)
  - Vankin, (George) Lawrence, 1958-1978; 4 folders (80 items) (Box 18)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Biographical and personal data; Evolution; Graduate study -- University of Rochester; Human evolution, physical anthropology; Molecular genetics; Mouse genetics; Population genetics; Publication; Recommendations; Requests for aid in finding positions
  - Vasil, Indra K., 1975-1978; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Vielkind, Jurgen, 1977-1979; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Vishniac, Wolf V., 1965-1966; 2 folders (25 items) (Box 18)
    Educational matters; Recommendations; Stanford University; University of Rochester
  - Waelsch, Salome Gluecksohn (Box 18)
  - Wagner, Robert P., 1972 (Box 18)
  - Wallace, Bruce, 1955-1971; 2 folders (22 items) (Box 18)
    Biographical and personal data; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Drosophila genetics; Fellowships, assistantships; Genetics; Population genetics; Recommendations
  - Walsh, Charles, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Washburn, Sherwood L., 1960-1973 (Box 18)
  - Wassermann, Felix, 1957, 1966 (Box 18)
  - Watson, Geoffrey S., 1957-1977; 6 folders (91 items) (Box 19)
    Bibliographical matters; Biographical and personal data; Cytogenetics; Editorial matters; Evolution; Genetics of plants; Molecular genetics; Population genetics; Protozoan genetics; Recommendations; Research support; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Watson, James, 1968, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Watson, Margaret L., 1968 (Box 19)
  - Wehrmaker, Alfred, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropological Research, 1964-1968 (Box 19)
  - Wescott, Roger, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
  - Wesleyan University, 1954-1970; 7 folders (102 items) (Box 19)
    Biographical and personal data; Evolution; Genetics; Graduate study; Recommendations; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Teaching -- Wesleyan University; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Wesleyan University
  - West, David A., 1968 (Box 19)
  - Westergaard, Mogens, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Whiting, Anna R., 1961 (Box 19)
  - Whiting, Phineas W., 1960-1968 (Box 19)
  - Wolff, George L., 1971 (Box 19)
  - Wolsky, Alexander, 1955-1961 (Box 19)
  - Wright, Theodore R. F., 1962-1974 (Box 19)
  - Young, Elihu M., 1972-1974 (Box 19)
  - Zackin, S. Jerome, 1961 (Box 19)
  - Ziegler, Irmgard, 1958-1976; 4 folders (Box 19)
  - Zirkin, Barry R., 1970 (Box 19)